Dorothy Hamilton Brush Papers, 1840-1969 (bulk 1936-1968)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES (1840-49, 1923-67)
  - Birth control-themed rug: photos, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - [Original rug is in Oversize Materials]
  - Catholic Church publications
    - Birth control, 1923, 1930-58 n.d. (Box 9, Folder 6-9)
    - General (Box 9)
      - 1925, 1941-49 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - 1951-57, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Marriage and family, 1930-33, 1941-51, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3-6)
    - Sex, 1935, 1941, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Catholicism: articles and correspondence, 1941-42, 1950, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - China: magazines and pamphlets (M. Sanger and birth control), 1962-67 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Health and healthcare: pamphlets, 1943-44, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Japan: paperback books (relating to birth control movement), 1953-55, 1963-67 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Marriage and family, 1934, 1943-56, 1964, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Married Woman's Private Medical Companion by Dr. A.M. Mauriceau, 1849 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Pathfinder Fund, 1967-68, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - "Preg-No-Matic," Brooklawn-Park Laboratory, 1956, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Sex: pamphlets, 1947-51 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1943, 1950, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - Flat file (on top)
    - Birth control-themed hook rug, n.d., [see also photographs in SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES]